Guide to the School of Hotel Administration Center for Professional Development records, 1928-1987.
School of Hotel Administration Center for Professional Development records, 1928-1987
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Center for Professional Development records, 1928-1987.
28-06-2414
Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration. Center for Professional Development.
4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, photographs, reports, and other records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
General office files include summer school records, accounting records, general correspondence, housing records, photographs, and annual reports.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
General office files include summer school records, accounting records, general correspondence, housing records, photographs, and annual reports.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration. Center for Professional Development.
Subjects:
Hotel management--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission ofoffice of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Summer School, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Summer School, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Summer School, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Summer School, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Summer School, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Summer School, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Summer School, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Summer School, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Summer School, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Summer School, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Summer School, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Summer School, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Summer School, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Summer School, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Summer School, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Summer School, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Summer School, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Summer School, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Summer School, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Summer School, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Summer School, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Summer School, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Summer School, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Summer School, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Summer School, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Summer School, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Summer School, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Summer School, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Summer School, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Summer School, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Summer School, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Summer School, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- SS of the Pacific, 1959, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Summer School, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Summer School, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Summer School, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Summer School, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Summer School, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Summer School, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Summer School, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Summer School, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Summer School, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Summer School, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Summer School, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Summer School, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Summer School, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Summer School, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Summer School, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- General File, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Nigeria File, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- General File, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Summer Session, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Summer Session, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Summer Session, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Summer Session, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Summer Session, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- CPD Accounting, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- CPD Accounting, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- CPD Accounting, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- CPD Accounting, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- CPD Accounting, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- CPD Accounting, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- CPD Accounting, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- CPD Activities, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- CPD Air Force, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- CPD Air Force, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- CPD Binenkorb, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- CPD Carl Duisberg, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- CPD Carl Duisberg, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- CPD Carl Duisberg, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- CPD Carl Duisberg, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- CPD Carl Duisberg, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- CPD Catalog, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- CPD Catalog, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- CPD Catalog, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- CPD Catalog, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Certificate Samples (Box 2, Folder 21)
- CPD Certificates, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- CPD Certificates, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- CPD Certificates, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- CPD Certificates, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- CPD Certificates, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- CPD Classrooms, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- CPD Comments, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- CPD Comments, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- CPD Comments, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- CPD Comments, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- CPD Comments, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- CPD Computer, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- CPD Computer, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- CPD Computer, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- CPD Computer, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- CPD Computer, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- CPD General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- CPD General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- CPD General Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- CPD General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- CPD Course Costs, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- CPD Course Costs, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- CPD Course Details, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- CPD Course Details, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- CPD Course Plan, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- CPD Course Plan, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- CPD Course Plan, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- CPD Participant Evaluations, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- CPD Participant Evaluations, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- CPD History (Box 3, Folder 14)
- CPD Hotel, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- CPD Hotel, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- CPD Hotel, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- CPD Housing, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- CPD Housing, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- CPD Housing, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- CPD Housing, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- CPD Housing, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- CPD Housing, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- CPD Housing, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Independent Research (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Ney-Hennessey, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Ney-Hennessey, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Ney-Hennessey, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Ney-Hennessey, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- CPD Operations Tour, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Participant Path (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Photos - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Photos - Scholarship (Box 4, Folder 4)
- CPD Photos, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- CPD Photos, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- CPD Photos, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- CPD Photos, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- CPD Photos, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- CPD Photos, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- CPD Photos, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- CPD Photos, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- CPD Photos, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- CPD P.M. Seminars, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- CPD P.M. Seminars, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- CPD P.M. Seminars, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- CPD Problems, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- CPD Problems, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- CPD Promotion, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- CPD Promotion, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- CPD Promotion, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- CPD Promotion, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- CPD Promotion, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- CPD Registration, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- CPD Registration, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- CPD Registration, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- CPD Registration, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- CPD Report, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- CPD Report, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- CPD Report, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- CPD Report, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- CPD Report, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- CPD Report, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Scholarship Aid (Elie Assaf) [returned to office of origin, 5/23/89] (Box 4, Folder 33)
- CPD Scholarship Aid [returned to office of origin, 5/23/89], 1982 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- CPD Scholarship Aid [returned to office of origin, 5/23/89], 1986 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- CPD Scholarship Aid [returned to office of origin, 5/23/89], 1987 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- CPD Staff, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- CPD Staff, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- CPD Welcome Packet, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- CPD Wrap Up, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- CPD Wrap Up, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- CPD Wrap Up, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 42)